# PRIYANSHU VISHWAKARMA

<u>LinkedIn: Priyanshu Vishwakarma</u> <u>https://my-portfolio-f14f5.web.app</u>

https://github.com/Anaveragec0der

priyanshuvishwakarma445@gmail.com

+91 9140514196

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Well-qualified Web Developer. Six months of virtual experience and familiar with a wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of the process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities.

# SKILLS

- C++
- JavaScript
- Data Structures
- Algorithms
- React.is
- HTML5
- CSS3

- Bootstrap5
- jQuery
- Node.js
- Express.js
- API
- Git | GitHub
- MongoDB

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **VISUROYTHM**

- This Web Application allows users to visualize various sorting algorithms, user defined data can be added so that they can visualize sorting on it.
- Technology Used : React.js.
- <a href="https://visuorythm.web.app/">https://visuorythm.web.app/</a>

#### **PERSONAL SITE**

- The personal site contains fundamental information about me, including my skills, work experience, projects, etc.
- Technology Used: HTML5, CSS3, Bootctrap5, JavaScript, Express.js.

https://my-portfolio-f14f5.web.app

### **EDUCATION**

- MASTERS IN COMPUTER APPLICATIONS
   MMMUT Gorakhpur | 2021 - 2023
   8.0/10 GPA
- BACHELORS IN COMPUTER APPLICATIONS

VSICS Kanpur | 2017-2020 67.5%

## WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT END SOFTWARE ENGINEERING VIRTUAL EXPERIENCE

SKYSCANNER | SEPTEMBER 2022 - DECEMBER 2022

- HTMT5 | CSS3 | Bootstrap | JavaScript | jQuery | API
- Create Front End Web Apps

POWER
PROGRAMMER
VIRTUAL
EXPERIENCE

INFOSYS | JUNE 2022 -SEPTEMBETR 2022

- Algorithmic Thinking | Problem-Solving | Code Debugging | Advanced Data Structures
- Software Development Methodologies: Waterfall
- and Agile | Software Architecture

#### CERTIFICATION

- Power Programmer Virtual Experience | Infosys
- Front end software engineering virtual experience | Skyscanner
- Complete Web Development Bootcamp | Udemy
- DSA with C++ | Udemy